# **Norbertas Lapenas**

Mobile: 085 114-9751 27 The Meadows, Email: <a href="mailto:nlapenas@gmail.com">nlapenas@gmail.com</a> Oldgrange Wood, Website: <a href="mailto:https://norbertasl.github.io/">https://norbertasl.github.io/</a> Monasterevin,

GitHub: https://github.com/NorbertasL Co.Kildare.

### **Personal Profile**

An individual with a positive attitude and a natural understanding of logical thinking. Skilled at problem solving in a calm and organized manner. A team player with a self motivated mentality. Currently seeking the opportunity to start a career in "Software Development"

## **Education, Qualification & Training**

**2019** Full Stack Developer Course – On-line with Code Institute

2019 County Kildare Leader Partnership, Jigginstown, Naas, Co Kildare

**Business Development Course** 

Marketing QQI Level 5

**2016** Java SE 8 Associate Programmer Certificate

2010 Moyle Park College, Clondalkin, Dublin

Junior and Leaving Certificates completed. Best

student awards in 3<sup>rd</sup> and 5<sup>th</sup> year.

# **Key Skills Software Development & Achievement**

#### Front End Skills Back End Skills:

HTML / HTML5	<ul><li>Java / Spring</li></ul>
<ul> <li>CSS / CCS3 / Bootstrap</li> </ul>	Python / Django
<ul><li>JavaScript / jQuery / AngularJS</li></ul>	SQL / noSQL
Responsive Design	REST API

#### **General Skills:**

Version Control /Git	Team Player
Problem Solver	Self-Motivated/Self Driven
Maven framework	<ul> <li>Excellent communication skills</li> </ul>

# **Career Summary**

**2010-2019** A Gilligan Builders, Ballymount Drive, Ballymount, Dublin 12

Role Construction Operative/Installer

Full time and part-time role since 2010. A high number of duties and responsibilities required a fast learning mentality and excellent communicative skills. Problem-solving skills were essential for this position.

**2017-2018** Brendan McGee Construction, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

**Role** Construction Operative

Short-term role in a very fast pace building site environment. The role involved work-flow management and working as part of big teams.

**2015-2017** Junction 14 Service Station, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

**Role** Delicatessen Assistant

Key roles and repositories involved serving customers in a very fast pace and busy environment. Great communication and interpersonal skills were a necessity. Excellent teamwork and time management skills were developed in this role.

**2014-2015** Oxigen Environmental, Naas, Co Kildare

Role Environmental Refuse Collector

Part of a team of environmental refuse collectors providing a refuse collection service to customers throughout county Kildare.

### **Hobbies and Interests**

- 3D Printing(I assembled my own in 2018).
- Electronics, I tinker with Arduino and Raspberry Pi.
- Motorbike and driving on the country roads.
- Mixed Martial Arts BJJ.
- Cycling Cycled from Netherlands to France just for the fun of it.
- A lot of reading I'm a real book-work, because books are the best way to learn something new.

### References

References available on request.